wsvn.com 2019-12-07

# PRIVACY POLICY – WSVN 7News | Miami News, Weather, Sports | Fort Lauderdale

LAST UPDATED:  May 30, 2019

**Privacy Policy**

Sunbeam Television Corp. (“we,” or “us”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe how we collect, use, and disclose Personal Information that you submit to us and that we collect through the WSVN and WHDH-TV websites, [http://www.wsvn.com](http://www.wsvn.com/) and [http://www.whdh.com](http://www.whdh.com/) (“Sites”).   This Privacy Policy applies to anyone accessing or visiting our Sites (collectively, “you”).

**Information We Collect**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information is information about you that can be used to identify you, which may include, for example, your name, postal address, email address, phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with that information.  We may collect and use certain Personal Information in order to offer, maintain, provide, improve, and administer our Sites and services, including to provide news information, and to offer you additional information on our services and other offerings (collectively, “Services”), including:

  * **When you communicate with us, engage with our Sites, or sign up for materials.** We collect Personal Information, such as your email address or contact information and other information you may submit, when you communicate with us, sign up to receive our newsletter, publications, subscriptions, news, offers, promotional materials, or other information, or otherwise submit information through the Sites.  We may also collect Personal Information when you engage with content on or interact with our Sites, such as when you view a video.

  * **When you participate in surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or rewards or other programs.** We may request or otherwise collect Personal Information, such as your name, email address, and other contact information, when you enroll or participate in surveys, contests, sweepstakes, or rewards or other programs.  Participation in these programs is voluntary.

  * **When you apply for a job with us.** We may collect Personal Information from you when you apply for a job with us, such as if you submit your resume for consideration.

  * **When we collect data from third parties or publicly-available sources.** We may obtain certain data about you from third-party sources to help us provide and improve the Services and for marketing and advertising.  We may combine your Personal Information with data we obtain from our Services, other users, or third parties to enhance your experience and improve the Services.

  * **When we leverage and/or collect cookies, device IDs, location data, data from the environment, and other tracking technologies.** We may collect certain Personal Information using cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, device IDs, geolocation, HTML5 local storage, Flash cookies, and IP addresses. We specifically use browser cookies for different purposes, including cookies that are strictly necessary for functionality and cookies that are used for personalization, performance/analytics, and advertising. Our “Cookies and Similar Technologies” section contains more information and options to control or opt-out of certain data collection or uses.

You are not required to provide all Personal Information identified in this Privacy Policy in order to use the Sites; however, please note that if you do not provide the Personal Information requested, we may be unable to provide some or all of the Services to you.

**Information Use and Disclosure**

We may use the Personal Information we collect in order to offer, maintain, provide, improve, and administer the Sites and Services, including:

  * To communicate with you regarding the Services, features, and other offerings;
  * To register you for contests, promotions, and sweepstakes, and to notify contest winners and award prizes;
  * To send surveys in connection with our Services;
  * For marketing purposes, including to contact you about offers, products, promotions, subscriptions, developments or services which we think may be of interest to you, and for third parties’ marketing purposes in connection with our Services;
  * To develop, provide, and improve our Sites and Services, including to better tailor the features, performance and support of our Services, and for statistical and analytics purposes;
  * To assist in the investigation of suspected illegal or wrongful activity, and to protect and defend our rights and property, or the rights or safety of third parties;
  * To enforce our Terms of Services, this Privacy Policy, or agreements with third parties;
  * To comply with laws, regulators, court orders, or other legal obligations, or pursuant to legal process.

We may disclose your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, including:

  * We may disclose some or all of your Personal Information to our subsidiaries, joint ventures, and other companies under our common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  Where we share Personal Information with our Affiliates, we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

  * **Service Providers and Vendors.** We may disclose Personal Information to distributors, service providers, marketing partners, payment processors, and vendors in order to maintain the Sites and provide, improve, and personalize the products and Services, including to fulfill a request for programs or services.  We may also share Personal Information for other technical and processing functions, such as sending e-mails on our behalf, fulfilling orders, technical support, or otherwise operating the Sites, for analytics, and for marketing and advertising purposes.

  * **Pursuant to Legal Process and Protection of Rights and Interests.** We may also disclose Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant, or other lawful request for information we receive, or as otherwise pursuant to legal process. We may also use and disclose Personal Information to establish or exercise our legal rights, to enforce our Terms of Services or this Privacy Policy, to assert and defend against legal claims, or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding actual or suspected illegal or fraudulent activities or potential threats to the physical safety or well-being of any person.

  * **Business Transactions.** Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to transfer some or all Personal Information in our possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other sale or transfer of all or a portion of our assets, including for the purpose of permitting the due diligence required to decide whether to proceed with a transaction. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, if the sale occurs, the purchaser will be entitled to use and disclose the Personal Information collected by us, and the purchaser will assume the rights and obligations regarding Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We use cookies and similar technologies to enhance and customize your experience on the Sites and for analytics.  We also use cookies and similar technologies for purposes of marketing and advertising, including interest-based advertising.

A “cookie” is a small text file that a web server stores in browser software.  A browser sends cookies to a server when the browser makes a connection to the server (for example, when requesting a web page from the same domain that created the cookie). The purpose of cookies is to remember the browser over time and distinguish one browser instance (or user) from all others.  Some cookies and other technologies may serve to track Personal Information previously entered by a web user on our Site. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them, and how to remove them. Cookies can remember login information, preferences, and similar information.

Cookies, as well as other tracking technologies such as HTML5 local storage, and Local Shared Objects (such as “Flash” cookies), and similar mechanisms, may record information such as a unique identifier, information you enter in a form, IP address, and other categories of data.

We also use web beacons or “pixels,” and in certain circumstances may collect IP address, screen resolution and browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns, dates and times that our site is accessed, and other categories of data.

If you want to block the use and saving of cookies from the Sites on to the computer’s hard drive, you should take the necessary steps within your web browser’s settings to block all cookies from the Sites and their external serving vendors.  Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain parts of our Sites may not function correctly. For information on how to disable cookies, refer to your browser’s documentation.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

Interest-based advertising is advertising that is targeted to you based on your web browsing and app usage over time and across websites or apps. You have the option to restrict the use of information for interest-based advertising and to opt-out of receiving interest-based ads. Depending on from where you access our Sites, you may also be asked to consent to our use of cookies, including advertising cookies.

The opt-outs for interest-based advertising require that strictly necessary cookies are not blocked by the settings in your web browser. We support the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising of the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) in the U.S., the [Canadian Digital Advertising Alliance](https://youradchoices.ca/) in Canada, and the [European Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.edaa.eu/European-principles/) in the EU. If you live in the United States, Canada, or the European Union, you can visit [Ad Choices](http://optout.aboutads.info/) (US), [Your Ad Choices](http://youradchoices.ca/choices/) (Canada), or [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) (EU) to find a convenient place to opt-out of interest-based advertising with participating entities for each region. These websites also provide detailed information about how interest-based advertising works. Opting out does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising from us, or when you use the Internet. It just means that the data collected from our website will not be used for interest-based advertising and that the advertising you see displayed on websites will not be customized to your interests.

**DO-NOT-TRACK**

Do-Not-Track is a public-private initiative that has developed a “flag” or signal that an Internet user may activate in the user’s browser software to notify websites that the user does not wish to be “tracked” by third-parties as defined by the initiative. The online community has not agreed on what actions, if any, should be taken by the websites that receive the “do not track” signal, and therefore Do-Not-Track is not yet standardized. Please note that the Sites do not alter their behavior or use practices when we receive a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**Social Network Widgets**

Our Sites may include social network sharing widgets that may provide information to their associated social networks or third parties about your interactions with our web pages that you visit, even if you do not click on or otherwise interact with the plug-in or widget. Information may be transmitted from your browser and may include an identifier assigned by the social network or third party, information about your browser type, operating system, device type, IP address, and the URL of the web page where widget appears. If you use social network tools or visit social networking sites, we encourage you to read their privacy disclosures, to learn what information they collect, use, and share.

**De-Identified or Anonymized Data**

We may create de-identified or anonymous data from Personal Information by removing data components (such as your name, email address, or linkable tracking ID) that makes the data personally identifiable to you or through obfuscation or through other means.  Our use of de-identified and anonymized data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Information from Children Under 13 Years of Age**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information online from individuals under 13 years without parental consent.  If you become aware that an individual under 13 years of age has provided us with Personal Information without parental consent, please contact us at _privacypolicy@wsvn.com_ or the address listed in the “Contact Us” section of this Privacy Policy.  If we become aware that an individual under 13 years has provided us with Personal Information without parental consent, we will take steps to remove the data as permitted by law.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Sites may contain links or otherwise provide access to another website, mobile application, or Internet location (collectively “Third-Party Sites”). We provide these links merely for your convenience. We have no control over, do not review, and are not responsible for Third-Party Sites, their content, or any goods or services available through the Third-Party Sites. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to Third-Party Sites.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any Third-Party Sites with which you choose to interact.

**Opting-Out of Certain Communications**

If you want to stop receiving future marketing messages and materials, you can do so by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included in our email marketing messages or by contacting us at _privacypolicy@wsvn.com_ or the contact information listed in the “Contact Us” section of this Privacy Policy. Once you have submitted your email address to “unsubscribe,” please note that you may continue to receive emails for a period of time while our system updates your request.  Please note that you may continue to receive communications from us for non-marketing purposes, such as communications regarding the Services.

**Processing in the United States**

Please note that if you are visiting the Sites from outside of the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored, and/or processed in the United States.  The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country.  If you are located outside of the United States, the transfer of Personal Information is necessary to provide you with the requested information, products, and services and/or to perform any requested transaction.  By using any portion of the Sites, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States.

**Security**

We implement technical and organizational security safeguards designed to protect your Personal Information. However, please be advised that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with the storage and transmission of Personal Information.

**Accessing or Updating Your Information**

Subject to applicable law, you may also make a request to access, update, correct, modify, or delete your Personal Information that we maintain by contacting us at  _privacypolicy@wsvn.com_ or the contact information listed in the “Contact Us” section of this Privacy Policy.

**California Privacy Rights**

Under Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information (as defined by California law) the business shares with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by emailing us at _privacypolicy@wsvn.com_ with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. Be sure to provide in the request sufficient information to properly identify you and/or the members of your family.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page to stay informed of how we may process your information.

**Contact**

For questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
